Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 61, folder: 18 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: We;come to Stromberg-Carlson, Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Organization Chart No. 1A, Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Box: 61, folder: 19 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Stromberg-Carlson Company and Rochester Independent Workers, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Stromberg-Carlson Company and Rochester Independent Workers, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
    July 25, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Memorandum of Understanding, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Stromberg-Carlson Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Box: 61, folder: 20 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: How to Get Ideas that Pay Off, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: the speaker, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Box: 61, folder: 21 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: 100 Years on the Road, Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: A Trip Through the Studebaker Factory, Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Box: 61, folder: 22 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Your New Career: it's benefits and opportunities, Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Box: 61, folder: 23 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Older Workers Lifeline: A Free Employment Referral Service, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: SAGE, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: STOP and thinkabout employing a senior citizen, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: SAGE, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: 11th Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Older Workers Lifeline: A Free Employment Service, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Retired?, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: SAGE, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: SAGE/OWL Older Workers Lifeline, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Box: 61, folder: 24 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Creed We Work By, Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Automation and the Problems of Management, Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Box: 61, folder: 25 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Reports: Public Relations in Industry, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Sun Oil Company 1962 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Sun Oil Company 1962 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Sun Oil Company 1961 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Sun Oil Company 1959 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Sun Oil Company 1955 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Sun Oil Company 1957 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Sun Oil Company 1958 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Sun Oil Company 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Sun Oil Company 1968, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Sun Oil Company 1969, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: Sun Oil Company 1971, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Box: 61, folder: 26 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Seeking an Agenda for Americans, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
    By Robert G. Dunlop. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Challenge of Industrial Change, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: The Challenge of Free Markets, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Box: 61, folder: 27 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Inside SMI, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Index of Super Market Articles, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: How Super Market Institute Serves Its Members and Its Industry, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Box: 61, folder: 28 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Super Market Industry Speaks, Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: The Super Market Industry Speaks, Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Box: 61, folder: 29 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: By-Laws: Susquehanna Valley Law Enforcement Association, Publication (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Box: 61, folder: 30 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Annual Report: year ended December 31, 1952, Publication (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Box: 61, folder: 31 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The American Scene, Publication (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Box: 61, folder: 32 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan Policy, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Report to Employes, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
    January 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Liquidation Sale, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Swift News, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Liquidation Sale, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Packinghouse Machinery and Equipment Sale Now in Progress at Montgomery, Alabama, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Box: 61, folder: 33 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan Policy, Publication (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Box: 61, folder: 34 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Bulletin 061, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Company Information Sheet for Swift & Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Company Information Sheet for Swift & Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Swift Fact Book, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Spring Breezes are Blowing Bargains Your Way!, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: Storeroom Parts & Supplies for Specific Machinery: We Invite You to Bid on Each Lot Number, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 7: Catalogue Sale of Used Machinery and Equipment, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 8: Packing House Machinery & Equipment Catalogue Sale, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
- Box: 61, folder: 35 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employes Representation Plan for the Plants of Swift & Co., Publication (Box 61, Folder 35)
    November 1, 1921. Item is in English.
- Box: 61, folder: 36 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Graduating Into Industry, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Patterned Interview--Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Secure Your Future with Swift & Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Opportunities for Engineers and Scientists with Swift, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Your Job with Swift, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 6: Employment Opportunities with Swift & Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 7: Secure Your Future with Swift & Compan: A Leader in the Food Industry, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Department Organization Chart, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 9: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 10: Supervisor Personnel Analysis Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 11: Personnel Analyss Report, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
- Box: 61, folder: 37 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Mark, Publication (Box 61, Folder 37)
- Box: 61, folder: 38 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Sylvania: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: The Sylvania Story, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Information Sheet, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: The Sylvania Electronic Systems Story, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Item 5: Career Opportunities in Finance, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
- Box: 61, folder: 39 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Human Dignity, Publication (Box 61, Folder 39)
    By Don G. Mitchell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Background Information from Sylvania, Publication (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Background Information from Sylvania, Publication (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: The Sylvania Story, Publication (Box 61, Folder 39)
- Box: 61, folder: 40 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: Camillus Sylvania News, Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
    June 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 61, folder: 41 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job, Publication (Box 61, Folder 41)
- Box: 61, folder: 42 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: On the Staff at Syracuse University, Publication (Box 61, Folder 42)
    July 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 61, folder: 43 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Professional Systems Course, Publication (Box 61, Folder 43)
- Box: 62, folder: 1 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Tally Industries, Inc.: 1970 Second Quarter and Six Months Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Information about Monsanto, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Box: 62, folder: 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Clerical Unit Contract between Stanolind Employees Federation and Stanolind Oil and Gas Company, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Clerical Unit Contract between Stanolind Employees Federation and Stanolind Oil Gas Company, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Clerical Unit Contract between Stanolind Employees Federation and Stanolind Oil and Gas Company, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: General Labor Relations Agreement: Talon, Inc. & Local Unions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    January 8, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: General Labor Relations Agreement: Talon, Inc. & Local Unions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Box: 62, folder: 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Tamiment Library, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Box: 62, folder: 4 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual Report: Tamiment Institute and Library, Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    June 1957-June 1958. Item is in English.
- Box: 62, folder: 5 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Taylor Standards: Industrial Relations Division Organizaion Chart, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A Warm Welcome to You, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Box: 62, folder: 6 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Taylor Meteor, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    March 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Tracking Down the 'Big Idea', Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Box: 62, folder: 7 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Plan for Employees' Represetation, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Box: 62, folder: 8 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Annual Report Teachers Insurance & Annuity Association of America for the year 1953, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: College Retirement Equites Fund, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: TIAA Cref 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Box: 62, folder: 9 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Telephone Pioneer, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: The Telephone Pioneer, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Telephone Pioneer, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Box: 62, folder: 10 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Investigation of Conectration of Economic Power, Publication (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Box: 62, folder: 11 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Division of University Extension: Annual Report 40th Year, Publication (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Box: 62, folder: 12 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Unversity of Tennessee Faculty Handbook, Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Box: 62, folder: 13 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Citizenship: our responsibilities to the American Dream, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Scott Paper Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Scott Paper Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Scott Paper Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The Scott Broadcast, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
    March 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: How Scott Paper Plans A Christmas Open House, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Public Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Scott Suggestion System, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Your Idea, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: The Scott Broadcast, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
    February 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Scott Paper Company Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Dateline: Marinette, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Highlights of the Cooperative Program of TVA and the Tennessee Valley Trades and Labor Council, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Ideas Wanter, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Employee Relationship Policy, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Box: 62, folder: 14 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Orientation Pamphlet for New Employees, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    By Thomas J. Saunders. Item is in English.
- Box: 62, folder: 15 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Texaco Star, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
    Number Three 1977. Item is in English.
- Box: 62, folder: 16 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Rising Affluence of America: 1963 Annual Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Box: 62, folder: 17 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Report to Texaco Employes on 1950 Operations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: 1902-1952 Report to Texaco Employes, Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: The Texas Company 1957 Annual Report, Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Box: 62, folder: 18 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Story of Texas Eastern, Publication (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Box: 62, folder: 19 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of Texas Employers' Insurance Association Rehabilitation Symposium, Publication (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Box: 62, folder: 20 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Welcome to TI Day One, Publication (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Box: 62, folder: 21 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Businessman in Civic and Political Affairs, Publication (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Box: 62, folder: 22 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: These Truths We Must Hold: a series of messages on American Freedoms, Publication (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Box: 62, folder: 23 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Your Job at University of Texas at Austin, Publication (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: The University of Texas Faculty Information Handbook, Publication (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Box: 62, folder: 24 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Red Menacea report to textileather employees from management, Publication (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Box: 62, folder: 25 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Your Life at Thatcher, Publication (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Box: 62, folder: 26 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Sixty-Ninth Annual Report of Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Company, Inc., Publication (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Box: 62, folder: 27 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Management of Thompson Products, Inc. and the Aircraft Workers Alliance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: 1950 Agreement between Management of Thompson Products, Inc. and the Aircraft Workers Alliance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: 1950 Agreement between Management of Thompson Products, Inc. and the Aircraft Workers Alliance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: 1950 Agreement between Management of Thompson Products, Inc. and the Aircraft Workers Alliance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: 1955 Agreement between Management of Thompson Products, Inc. and the Aircraft Workers Alliance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: 1955 Agreement between Management of Thompson Products, Inc. and the Aircraft Workers Alliance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Management's Pledge Grievance Procedure Seniority Agreement, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Management's Pledge Grievance Procedure Seniority Agreement, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: Statement of Raymond S. Livingstone to the Committee on Education and Labor of the House of Representatives, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
    February 24, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Can There be Industrial Peace with Unionism?, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: A Message from Ray Livingston, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Human Relations Policy, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: A TRW Declaration of Independence, Publication (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Box: 62, folder: 28 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: A Handbook or Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: 1950 Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Old Guard Associaiton, Publication (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Box: 62, folder: 29 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Here's the Typical Old Guard Member--, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: 1954 Annual Report to Employees, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: We'll be 50 Years Old Tomorrow, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Friendly Forum, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    October 17, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Friendly Forum, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Friendly Forum, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    March 7, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: To Members of the Thompson Organization, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    March 6, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Newsletter to Supervision, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    February 1, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Newsletter to Supervision, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    February 15, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Newsletter to Supervision, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    March 14, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Newsletter to Supervision, Publication (Box 62, Folder 29)
    January 4, 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 62, folder: 30 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Background for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Talk of the Month: Opportunity for Business, Publication (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Box: 62, folder: 31 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Executive Organization Chart, Publication (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Box: 62, folder: 32 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Human Relations Policy, Publication (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Box: 62, folder: 33 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: J. G. Tilp, Incorporated Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: J. G. Tilp, Incorporated Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Box: 62, folder: 34 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: How 18 Steel Problems Were Solved, Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Defending Management's Right to Manage, Publication (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Box: 62, folder: 35 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Positive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    By Herbert E. Markley. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Positive Employee Relations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Contract Neogitation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 27, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 29, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 18, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    June 23, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    October 8, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    October 12, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    October 14, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    October 20, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    February 12, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    February 11, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    February 10, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    February 15, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 10, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 7, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 30, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 3, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 4, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 5, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 6, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 16, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 17, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 21, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 2, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 23, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 28, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    July 29, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 30: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 31: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    September 22, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    September 16, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 6, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 14, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 11, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 12, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 13, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 14, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 17, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 18, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 19, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 20, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 21, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
    August 22, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 46: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 47: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 48: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 49: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 50: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Item 51: Contract Negotiation Digest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 35)